shopperstop.org 2014-05-19

# Privacy Policy : Shoppers Top Online Shopping Directory

**Privacy Policy:**

Shoppers Top understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide information about yourself in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at Shoppers Top more valuable to you. We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information Shoppers Top may collect how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use (the "Terms and Conditions of Use") posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the Terms and Conditions of Use. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the Terms and Conditions of Use.

**Cookies**

Shoppers Top may send a "cookie" to your computer. Cookies are used by many sites, an internet search on 'cookies' may provide you with more information that you will ever need. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. Shoppers Top will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most internet browser are set up to accept cookie. Although it is possible to reset your computer settings to inform you of cookie or to reject cookies, such actions may interfere with your searches at Shoppers Top.

**What information do we collect?**

Shoppers Top does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the site submission process. This information may be used to contact you if there is a need for a revision to your site reviews. Shoppers Top notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

**Uses of Information**

We use the information to help us understand more about how our website is used and to improve our site. Shoppers Top only use personal information for the purpose for which it was provided and certain other activities, which are reasonably ancillary to such purpose. For example, if you send us an e-mail with a question or comment, Shoppers Top will use your e-mail address to respond to you. Also, Shoppers Top may store your e-mail and e-mail address and a copy of our response for future reference. Shoppers Top may also use and disclose personal information that is relevant to a legal proceeding or as required by law.

**Do we share information?**

We do not sell your personal information to others. Some of our products are hosted by third parties but we agree with those third parties that they will keep your information secure and not use it for other purposes. If you sign up for services that are managed or offered by other organisations, they will obtain your information. A number of other people's websites have links on our site. If you link to their sites, they may collect information. Such sites are not within our control and are not covered by this privacy policy.

**How long is the Information Kept?**

Shoppers Top will only keep the personal information for so long as it is useful. At the conclusion of such time, "The Owners" will delete this information.

**Links to Other Sites**

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Shoppers Top searches are developed by people over whom Shoppers Top has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.

**Additional Information**

This site contains links to other sites. "The Owners" are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

We reserve the right to make changes to the privacy policy at any time. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes.

Any questions relating to this privacy policy may be sent through our contact page.
